Capstone.create([
  {project_name: "Busk", student_name: "Trent Childers", youtube_id: "hbKsj7a3k2s"},
  {project_name: "Devour", student_name: "Natasha Wu", youtube_id: "Mh_6Tlzm_YE"},
  {project_name: "Volunteer Management System", student_name: "Kimberly Lowe-Williams", youtube_id: "ywrjM5j8Zeo"},
  {project_name: "My Forecashter", student_name: "Nick Kang", youtube_id: "uBVIabVV-Qo"},
  {project_name: "ChefHat", student_name: "Mark Bouslog", youtube_id: "Sk0U_v1AT5A"},
])
Faq.create([
  {question: "Assuming I also have the ability to attend a full time program, why would I attend a part time program like yours?", answer: 'Most programs have very little instruction and instead provide material for the students with which they can teach themselves. By contrast, ACLTC has a 50/50 balance between instruction and exercises. The bottom line is that it takes a lot less time to learn something when it’s explained and demonstrated to you by expert educators than it does when you have to learn it on your own. We’ve actually had students who tried full time programs first before leaving and joining ours, and they’ve been shocked to experience the difference. In the words of one of them, "It took me 5 hours to learn what you just explained in 30 minutes, and it makes a lot more sense now."', priority: 0},
  {question: "What kind of people attend ACLTC?", answer: "Most people who attend ACLTC are looking to switch careers into web development. From police officers to ice cream store owners, individuals from all walks of life and background have attended our program.", priority: 1},
    {question: "What programming background do I need to be accepted into ACLTC?", answer: "While you certainly don’t need to be a programmer already (that’s why you’re looking into ACLTC, isn’t it?), we do expect our applicants to have been putting some effort into teaching themselves to code to some extent.", priority: 2 },
    {question: "What qualities do you look for when selecting students for ACLTC?", answer: "We seek students who are ambitious, eager to learn, and ready to handle frustration from time to time. We also have two other key requirements: The first is that you must be seeking a career in software engineering, and the second is that you must have been teaching yourself to code to some extent before joining our course.", priority: 3},
    {question: "To what extent must I have been teaching myself to code before joining the course?", answer: "It’s difficult to quantify this, and we judge this on a case by case basis. A typical applicant has been working on some online programming tutorials for a number of months.", priority: 4},
    {question: "If anyone can learn to code, why do you not accept everyone into your course?", answer: "To have an effective course, we need to ensure that all the students are coming in at the same skill level. Otherwise, we’d have a situation in which some students are bored while others fall behind.", priority: 5},
    {question: "Do you offer any financial assistance?", answer: "We have partnered with Pave, a lending institution that offers loans for tuition. One must first be accepted into ACLTC before applying for a loan through Pave. All of the other details can be found <a href='http://hello.pave.com/anyone' target='_blank'>here</a>.", priority: 6},
    {question: "How does payment work?", answer: "Assuming one does not secure a loan through Pave, payment is made in three phases. $1,000 must be put down as a non-refundable deposit in order to secure your spot in the course. Of the remainder, 50% is due by the first day of Phase 1, and the other 50% is due by the fifth week of Phase 2.", priority: 7},
    {question: "Can I set up a payment plan?", answer: "Other than getting a loan through Pave, we do not currently offer payment plans, unfortunately.", priority: 8},
    {question: "Do you have a refund policy?", answer: "If one voluntarily withdraws from the course within 30 days from the beginning of Phase 1, the tuition is refunded minus the $1,000 deposit.", priority: 9},
    {question: "What are the details of the application process?", answer: "The first step is to fill out the form <a href='http://goo.gl/forms/zrdY395j8w' target='_blank'>here</a>. Next, an Admissions Officer will reach out to schedule an interview over Skype. At the end of the interview, you will be given a brief programming exercise for homework (which includes watching some tutorial videos). Once you submit the homework, the Admissions Committee will review your entire application and inform you within one week whether you’ve been accepted to ACLTC. If you have, you will be given a student contract to review and sign. Once you’ve signed it, you can officially reserve your spot in the course by submitting a non-refundable deposit of $1,000 which goes towards your tuition.", priority: 10},
    {question: "What percentage of students get accepted to the program?", answer: "Of those that complete the entire interview process (including submitting the programming homework), approximately 70% are accepted.", priority: 11},
    {question: "What topics are covered during Phase 1 (prework)?", answer: "During the prework phase you will be working on the fundamentals of Ruby and programming in general. We also introduce you to Object Oriented Programming, and sneak in a tiny amount of HTML and CSS as well.", priority: 20},
    {question: "How much time will I be expected to put into Phase 1?", answer: "Phase 1 lasts for three weeks, and you should expect to commit to working on it for about twenty hours per week.", priority: 21},
    {question: "Can I do Phase 1 remotely?", answer: "Phase 1 is completely remote, so you can do it from wherever you'd like!", priority: 22},
    {question: "How is the curriculum of the in-person classes (Phase 2) laid out and how much do you focus on each technology?", answer: "During the first week, we cover essential tools including the command line, Git, and Github. We also review essential Ruby concepts that were introduced during the Prework (Phase 1). At the beginning of the second week, we cover HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap for just a day or two. That’s really all we cover regarding HTML/CSS, since the concepts are simple enough that you can pick up the rest of them on your own. We then jump right into Rails, and cover the fundamentals of Rails through the end of the the fifth week. During this time we also delve into SQL and database design. In the sixth week we begin to cover testing and TDD. and the students begin their individual Capstone Projects at this time, which they work on for about six hours per week. In the seventh week, we learn about APIs, first by consuming third party APIs, and then by building our own internal APIs. In the eighth week, we explore APIs in greater detail, as well as how to build microservices and API best practices. In the ninth week we jump into JavaScript, starting with plain JavaScript but then moving into AngularJS which continues until the end of the tenth week. The final two weeks are almost completely devoted to the Capstone projects, so that the they can be complete by the Showcase!", priority: 30},  
    {question: "What kind of project can I work on for the Capstone Project?", answer: "You will be working on a web application based on a topic that interests you. (This does not include mobile apps.) You will receive guidance from your instructor during the course to help you choose an application that is both impressive and reasonable. To see a sampling of past Capstone Projects, see <a href='/capstones' target='_blank'>here</a>.", priority: 31},
    {question: "Do I work on the capstone project by myself or with someone else?", answer: "Each student works on their own Capstone Project.", priority: 32},  
    {question: "Is there any homework during the course?", answer: "While Phase 1 consists solely of homework, there is no homework during Phase 2. We do encourage those who have extra time to put in some extra practice or to build out their Capstone Projects further. The more time you put in, the more you get out.", priority: 33},
    {question: "What is the teacher-to-student ratio?", answer: "There are typically between 13 to 20 students in a class. There is one lead instructor, and a number of Teaching Assistants (TAs). The number of TAs in the room depend on the number of students. During exercises and the time devoted to working on the Capstone Project, we strive to have one staff member per every five students.", priority: 34},
    {question: "What happens if I miss a class?", answer: "All instruction is recorded, and you will be provided with the instruction from that day. You will be expected to watch the instruction and complete the exercises as soon as possible, as each lesson typically builds upon the previous ones.", priority: 35},
    {question: "How do you help students find jobs?", answer: "At the end of the course, we organize The Showcase which is an opportunity for students to network and show off their Capstone Projects to local employers who are looking to hire development talent. We also assist in resume creation before the Showcase and providing ongoing advice to the students during the job hunting process.", priority: 40},
    {question: "What kind of job could I expect to land after completing the course?", answer: "Most of our graduates become developers/graduates/software engineers. Many of these start out as interns for a few months before being brought on by the company full time, while others begin right away as entry level developers.", priority: 41},
    {question: "Can I sit in on a class?", answer: "We love guests! Reach out to us at hello@anyonecanlearntocode to schedule a visit.", priority: 50},
    {question: "Is there a way I can talk to former graduates?", answer: "Definitely. Reach out to us at hello@anyonecanlearntocode and we can connect you to some of our alumni.", priority: 51},
    {question: "Is there a way to take this course remotely?", answer: "While Phase 1 is remote, Phase 2 (the main 12 week offering) takes place in a classroom in which you must be physically present.", priority: 60},
    {question: "How often does this course take place?", answer: "Currently, our Chicago course takes place six times a year, and our San Francisco course takes place three times a year.", priority: 61},
    {question: "I cannot make the upcoming course. Can I apply for a future course?", answer: "Absolutely!", priority: 62},
    {question: "What kind of hardware or software does my computer need to have? Does it matter what kind of computer I have for the class?", answer: "We require the use of Macbooks (2012 or later). If you do not have one, let us know and we’ll lend you one for the duration of the course. (And you can even take it home!)", priority: 70},
    {question: "How long has ACLTC been in existence?", answer: "ACLTC began in May 2014, graduating its very first class in August 2014.", priority: 80},
    {question: "I have some questions not listed here. How can I learn more?", answer: "Please reach out to us at hello@anyonecanlearntocode.com with any other questions you may have. To speak to someone live, we recommend that you begin the application process, and our Admissions Officer can answer your questions at length during the interview.", priority: 1000}

])

Screencast.destroy_all
Screencast.create([
    {priority: 1, name: "Intro To Ruby  ", youtube_id: "oUC0hNTZrzM"},
    {priority: 2, name: "Variables", youtube_id: "1jwwkolNEcs"},
    {priority: 3, name: "Objects and Classes", youtube_id: "sm5RI7baE6Y"},
    {priority: 4, name: "Methods", youtube_id: "vwD-xxyFrp8"},
    {priority: 5, name: "The Terminal", youtube_id: "ceXWZUii_bg"},
    {priority: 6, name: "Your First Ruby Program", youtube_id: "rNiTr8HMNLY"},
    {priority: 7, name: "Conditionals", youtube_id: "V01p6Yotg7c"},
    {priority: 8, name: "Loops", youtube_id: "LAxot1JTLZ4"},
    {priority: 9, name: "Arrays", youtube_id: "vaeXc2knEyU"},
    {priority: 10, name: "More About Arrays", youtube_id: "QYlDARCm4rw"},
    {priority: 11, name: "The Each Method", youtube_id: "zCzizprf538"},
    {priority: 12, name: "Experimentation", youtube_id: "ce67-VT9ATI"},
    {priority: 13, name: "Hashes", youtube_id: "p_i4W1aUi74"},
    {priority: 14, name: "Creating Classes", youtube_id: "bSBC_A1zokc"},
    {priority: 15, name: "Creating Methods", youtube_id: "alMLJIiUvBA"},
    {priority: 16, name: "Return Values", youtube_id: "-XI1ASw77ak"},
    {priority: 17, name: "Arguments", youtube_id: "PnFdTMzZHRE"},
    {priority: 18, name: "Instance Variables", youtube_id: "ypRrpgP6iLI"},
    {priority: 19, name: "Constructors", youtube_id: "H8W6KdFkPFI"},
    {priority: 20, name: "Getters", youtube_id: "TKv99qYgONs"}
])
puts "Done!"